A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 4, Accession 2017:060 FA1442
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 4, Accession 2017:060
1980-2014
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation
FA1442
30.4 Cubic Feet 80 letter-sized document boxes
Biographical / Historical
The Henry Luce Foundation was established by Henry R. Luce in 1936. As a New York-based nonprofit organization, the Luce Foundation awards grants in American Art, Asian studies, Higher Education, Theology, and supports the Clare Boothe Luce Program for women in science, mathematics, and engineering.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the Henry Luce Foundation in 2017.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 4) are arranged as follows:
Series 1: Project Files, 1990-2014
Series 2: American Art Conservation Initiative Files, 2006-2014
Series 3: Luce Fund for Southeast Asian Studies, 1982-2005
Series 4: Luce Fund for Chinese Scholars, 1980-2005
Scope and Contents
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 4) contain grant files and information on projects supported by the American Art Conservation Initiative, Luce Fund for Southeast Asian Studies, and Luce Fund for Chinese Scholars.
Related Materials
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 1, Accession 2017:057 (FA1317)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 2, Accession 2017:058 (FA1393)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 3, Accession 2017:059 (FA1410)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 5, Accession 2017:061 (FA1472)
Education (Higher); Religion; Theology; Asian studies; Art, American
- Project Files, 1990-2014; 1
  - Addison Gallery of American Art - Art Exhibition Exchange Program (ACE), 1998-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Addison Gallery of American Art - To Conserve a Legacy: American Art from Historically Black Colleges and Universities, 1996-2001 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Afro-American Historical and Cultural Museum - African-American Female Sculptors, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Albany Institute of History and Art - Documentation Project, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - All Souls Parish - Minister of Word and Sacrament, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Arts Alliance - Arts, Religion, and Public Support Conference, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - American Assembly - "The Arts and the Public Purpose" Conference, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - American Assembly - United States-China Clash: United States and Chinese Interests, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - American Association of Museums - Museum Assessment Program Review, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Council for Capital Formation/Center for Policy Research - Taxation Research, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American Council for the United Nations University - Awareness of the United Nations University, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - American Council for the United Nations University - Cultivating Contacts in the Knowledge Industry, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - American Council of Learned Societies - Committee on Scholarly Communications with China: Sino-Japanese War Period Catalog, 1994-1998 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
  - American Council of Learned Societies - Dissertation Program in American Art, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
  - American Craft Council - Jack Lenor Larsen Fund, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - American Craft Museum - The World of Beads, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - American Federation of Arts - Elie Nadelman: Classical Folk, 1997-2001 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - American Federation of Arts - Exhibition Initiatives, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 21-22)
  - American Federation of Arts - William Sidney Mount, 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 23-24)
  - American Judicature Society - Judicial Conduct and Ethics, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
  - American Museum of Natural History - Siberia Project, 1996-2000 (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
  - American Russian Young Artists Orchestra - Expansion and Development, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - American Russian Young Artists Orchestra - Renewed Support, 1998-2003 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - American Theological Library Association - Monograph Preservation Program (Renewal), 1993-2002 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - American Theological Library Association - Serials Preservation Program, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - American Theological Library Association - Demonstration CD-ROM (Box 5, Folder 32)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Amon Carter Museum - John Singer Sargent and Claude Monet: An Artistic Interaction, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Andover Newton Theological School - Summer Institute for Non-Hispanic Faculty, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Appeal of Conscience Foundation - American Religious Leaders Delegation to China, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Archives of American Art - Inventory and Catalog Collections, 1995-2001 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Arkansas Art Center - American Drawing Research Center, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 37-38)
  - Art Institute of Chicago - Mary Cassatt Exhibition, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 39-40)
  - Art Institute of Chicago - Research, Catalog, and Re-installation of American Art Collection, 1993-1997 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Art Kaleidoscope Foundation - Lenore Tawney: Art from Within, 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Art Restoration for Cultural Heritage - Bozidarevic (Madonna with Child and Saints) and Dobricevic (Our Lady with Child and Saints) Restoration, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Ashland University - William J. Casey Chair in Geopolitical Studies, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Asia Society - Ancient Arts of Vietnam: From River Plain to Open Sea, 2008-2010 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Asian Art Museum of San Francisco - Bali: Art, Ritual, Performance, 2009-2012 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Asian Art Museum of San Francisco - Court Arts of the Ming Dynasty, 2007-2012 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Asian Art Museum of San Francisco - Forum for Asian Art Museum Directors, 2010-2012 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Asian Art Museum of San Francisco - Mongol Renaissance Exhibit, 1994-2001 (Box 8, Folder 49-50)
  - Asian Cultural Council - Chinese Art History Initiative, 2002-2011 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Asian Cultural Council - Vietnamese Artist, Mrs. Bang Thuc Ban, 1997-2001 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Asian Cultural Council - Western Art and Art History Workshop, China Academy of Art (Hangzhou), 2011-2012 (Box 9, Folder 53-55)
  - Asian Cultural Council - Advanced Workshop in Western Art and Art History, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 53-55)
  - ASIANetwork - Consultancy Program, 1993-1998 (Box 9, Folder 56-57)
  - Associates of the University of Toronto - David Milne Catalog Raisonne, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Association for Asian Studies - Isolated Scholars of Southeast Asia, 1993-2000 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Association for Canadian Studies in the United States - Thomas O. Enders Endowment, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Association for Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Henry Luce III Fellows in Theology, 1993-1999 (Box 10, Folder 61-62)
  - Association to Unite the Democracies - Campaign for International Federation (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Association to Unite the Democracies - Streit Endowment Fund, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States - United States-China Interests in Central Asia, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Auburn Theological Seminary - Taking the Lead: Theological Education for Religious Leaders, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Australian National University - Economic History of Southeast Asia (ECHOSEA), 1991-1998 (Box 11, Folder 67-68)
  - Bangor Theological Seminary - Communication System, 1996-2003 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Bank Street College of Education - Institute of Educational Research and Public Policy (Liberty Partnerships Program), 1998-2003 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Bard Graduate Center for Studies in the Decorative Arts - Collaborative Program with the Brooklyn Museum, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Bass Museum of Art - The Making of Miami Beach, 1933-1942: Architecture of Lawrence Murray Dixon and Morris Lapidus, 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Bass Museum of Art - Atlantis (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Bass Museum of Art - Photo Documentation of Dixon Exhibition (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Baylor University - Christianity in China Symposium, 1995-1999 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Baylor University - George W. Truett Seminary, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Bennington Museum - Pottery Gallery and Study Center, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 75-76)
  - Bennington College - Regional Center for Language and Culture, 1996-1999 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Birmingham-Southern College - Service Learning Programs for At-Risk Youth (Urban At-Risk Children with Promise), 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Boston Public Library Foundation - American Art Collection, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 79-80)
  - Bowdoin College-Newman Center - Educational Materials to Catholic Clergy, 1995-2000 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - The Boys' Club of New York - Taking Responsibility Program, 1996-2000 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Boys Harbor, Inc. - Expansion of Technology Education Programs, 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 83-84)
  - Brandywine River Museum - Milk and Eggs: The American Revival of Tempera Painting, 1930-1950, 1999-2002 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Bridge to Asia Foundation - Information Transfer Station in Law (Serving 100 Returned Legal Scholars in China), 1994-2000 (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - Bronx Council on the Arts - Arthandlers Training Program, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Brookgreen Gardens - American Masters Sculpture Exhibit Tour (ACE), 1998-2001 (Box 14, Folder 88-89)
  - Brookings Institution - Financial Reform in China, 1997-2002 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Brookings Institution - New Members of Congress Seminar, 1992-1995 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Brookings Institution - Newly Elected Members of Congress #8, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music - Visual Arts Initiative, 1994-1999 (Box 15, Folder 93-94)
  - Brooklyn Historical Society - Catalog of Brooklyn-Related Works on Paper, 1994-1999 (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Brooklyn Museum - Eastman Johnson: Painting America, 1996-2000 (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Brooklyn Museum of Art - William Merritt Chase: Modern American Landscapes, 1886-1890, 1999-2001 (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - The Browning School - Henry Luce III Art Center, 1999-2003 (Box 16, Folder 98-99)
  - Bush Presidential Library Foundation - George Bush Presidential Library Center, 1995-2003 (Box 16, Folder 100)
  - Cambridge University Press - Shitao: His Life and Work, 1997-2001 (Box 16, Folder 101)
  - Canterbury Shaker Village - Art and Architecture of the Canterbury Shakers, 1992-1999 (Box 16, Folder 102)
  - Caramoor Center for Music and the Arts - Facility Renewal Campaign, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine - Choir Japan Tour, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies - Non-State Armed Movements, Religion and Service Provision, 2009-2012 (Box 17, Folder 105-106)
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies - Religion in Conflict-Prone Settings, 2005-2011 (Box 17, Folder 107-109)
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies/Pacific Forum CSIS - Young Leaders Program (Renewal), 2008-2012 (Box 18, Folder 110)
  - Center for Urban Pedagogy - Staff Recognition Grant (Li Ling), 2011-2012 (Box 18, Folder 111)
  - F.Y. Chang Foundation - American Studies Initiative in China (United States-China Education Trust Program), 2008-2011 (Box 18, Folder 112)
  - China Institute in America - Royal Tombs at Mawangdui: Art and Life in the Changsha Kingdom, 2008-2010 (Box 18, Folder 113)
  - Chinati Foundation - Handbook on Chinati History and Collections, 2008-2010 (Box 18, Folder 114)
  - Chrysler Museum on Art - American Art Collection, 2006-2011 (Box 18, Folder 115)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum - Curatorial Research Assistants (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2012 (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - Colby College Museum of Art - What is American Art? Symposium, 2008-2010 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - Columbia Theological Seminary - Cultural and Academic Exchanges (Columbia, China Christian Council, Nanjing Theological Seminary), 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - Columbia University - Cinema China, Culture China: A Chinese Film and Culture Festival, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - Columbia University - Professorship in Modern Tibetan Studies, 2003-2011 (Box 19, Folder 120-121)
  - Columbia University - Religion, Toleration, and Democracy in the World, 2006-2011 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Columbia University (East Asian Institute) - Asia in the Core Curriculum, 1993-1998 (Box 20, Folder 123)
  - Columbus Museum of Art - Claude Raguet Hirst Exhibit, 2002-2010 (Box 20, Folder 124)
  - Congressional Research Service (Library of Congress) - Orientation for New Members of the 112th Congress, 2010-2011 (Box 20, Folder 125-127)
  - Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum - Online National Design Museum Digitization Project, 2008-2011 (Box 20, Folder 128)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art - Pre-1945 American Paintings and Sculpture Catalog, 2002-2011 (Box 21, Folder 129-130)
  - Cornell College - Peter Paul Luce Gallery, 1998-2011 (Box 21, Folder 131)
  - Council of Independent Colleges - Liberal Arts Symposium, 2010-2011 (Box 21, Folder 132)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Membership Dues, 2004-2008 (Box 21, Folder 133)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Religion and Foreign Policy, 2006-2011 (Box 21, Folder 134-135)
  - The Council for Religion in Independent Schools (CRIS) - Regional Representatives, 1992-1998 (Box 21, Folder 136)
  - Crocker Art Museum - American Art Collection, 2009-2011 (Box 22, Folder 137)
  - Crocker Art Museum - American Art Collection Untitled CD (Box 22, Folder 137)
  - Currier Museum of Art - American Art Collection, 2007-2010 (Box 22, Folder 138)
  - Dayton Art Institute - Chief Curator Position (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2012 (Box 22, Folder 139)
  - Delaware Art Museum - Associate Art Curator of Contemporary Art (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2012 (Box 22, Folder 140)
  - Delaware Art Museum - Howard Pyle: American Master Rediscovered, 2010-2012 (Box 22, Folder 141)
  - Denver Art Museum - American Indian Art Collection, 2007-2011 (Box 22, Folder 142-143)
  - Denver Art Museum - Charles Deas: Telling Tales to 1840s America, 2004-2011 (Box 23, Folder 144-145)
  - Denver Art Museum - Interpreting American Design, 1975-2000, 1997-2005 (Box 23, Folder 146-147)
  - Detroit Institute of Arts - American Paintings Volume III, 2003-2005 (Box 23, Folder 148)
  - Detroit Institute of Arts - Maintain American Art Collection, 2010-2011 (Box 23, Folder 149)
  - Detroit Institute of Arts - Reframing of Late 19th Century American Paintings, 2009-2011 (Box 23, Folder 150)
  - Dia Art Foundation - Anthology of Essays on the Works of Agnes Martin, 2007-2011 (Box 24, Folder 151)
  - Dia Center for the Arts - Dan Flavin Catalog Raisonne Project, 1997-2006 (Box 24, Folder 152)
  - EastBridge - Publication Series on the Missionary Enterprise in Asia, 2004-2011 (Box 24, Folder 153)
  - East-West Center - South Korea-United States Journalist Exchange Program (Renewal), 2008-2009 (Box 24, Folder 154)
  - East-West Center/University of Hawaii - Asian Studies Development Program, 1996-2011 (Box 24, Folder 155-156)
  - East-West Center/University of Hawaii - Asian Studies Development Program (Renewal), 1999-2011 (Box 25, Folder 157)
  - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowship - China Program, 1994-1998 (Box 25, Folder 158)
  - El Museo del Barrio - Nexus: New York 1900-1945, Encounters in the Modern Metropolis, 2007-2011 (Box 25, Folder 159)
  - El Museo del Barrio - Research and Catalog the Permanent Collection, 2006-2010 (Box 25, Folder 160)
  - Emory University - Library Project (Harvard and Yale), 1993-1999 (Box 25, Folder 161-162)
  - Exit Art - Digital Archive Project, 2004-2010 (Box 26, Folder 163)
  - Farnsworth Art Museum - Bridge Funds for Endowment Campaign (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 164)
  - Figge Art Museum - Grand Wood Archives Project, 2006-2012 (Box 26, Folder 165)
  - Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco - Richard Diebenkorn Catalogue Raisonne, 2005-2011 (Box 26, Folder 166)
  - Flint Institute of Arts - American Art Collection Catalog (American Collections Enhancement), 1999-2006 (Box 26, Folder 167-168)
  - Flint Institute of Arts - Associate Curator, Assistant Registrar, Storage Racks from the American Art Renewal Fund (AARF), 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 169)
  - Florence Griswold Museum - Griswold House Interpretive Program, 2003-2010 (Box 27, Folder 170)
  - The Foundation Center - Membership Dues, 2004-2009 (Box 27, Folder 171)
  - The Frick Collection - American School Photograph Archive Digitization, 2010-2012 (Box 27, Folder 172)
  - Gadjah Mada University - Religious Studies Exchange Program for American and Indonesian Graduate Students, 2008-2012 (Box 27, Folder 173-175)
  - Sidney D. Gamble Foundation for China Studies - Exhibition of Gamble's Photographs in China, 1994-2000 (Box 28, Folder 176)
  - Gamble House, University of South Carolina - A New Native Beauty: The Art and Craft of Greene and Greene, 2007-2010 (Box 28, Folder 177)
  - German Marshall Fund of the United States - 150 Years of American Art: 1800-1950, Bucerius Kunst Forum, Germany, 2006-2011 (Box 28, Folder 178-179)
  - Graduate Theological Union - State of Theological Education, 1994-1998 (Box 28, Folder 180)
  - Grantmakers in the Arts - Annual Conference, 2009-2010 (Box 29, Folder 181)
  - Grantmakers in the Arts - Annual Conference: Navigating the Art of Change 2.0, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 182)
  - Gray Art Gallery - Park Avenue Cubists: Gallatin, Morris, Frelinghuysen, and Shaw, 2000-2004 (Box 29, Folder 183)
  - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum - Art in America: 300 Years of Innovation, 1998-2010 (Box 29, Folder 184-186, Box 30, Folder 187-188)
    Scope and Contents
    Also known as "American 300" a survey of American Art to be presented in China.
  - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum - Art in America Shanghai Installation Photos (Box 29, Folder 184-186, Box 30, Folder 187-188)
  - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum - John Chamberlain: Choices, 2011-2012 (Box 30, Folder 189)
  - Hamilton College - Associate Colleges in China Advanced Language Study, 2007-2012 (Box 30, Folder 190-191)
  - Hammer Museum, University of California, Los Angeles - Now Dig This!: Art and Black Los Angeles, 1960-1980, 2008-2012 (Box 31, Folder 192)
  - Harvard University - Symposium in Honor of Professor Akira Iriye, 2004-2011 (Box 31, Folder 193)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute - China Historical Geographic Information System Project, 2000-2011 (Box 31, Folder 194-195)
  - Heard Museum - Native American Collection, 2003-2010 (Box 31, Folder 196)
  - Heckscher Museum of Art - Collections Management/Digitization Project, 2004-2010 (Box 31, Folder 197)
  - Heckscher Museum of Art - Paper Chase: Works on Paper by William Merritt Chase and his Contemporaries, 2008-2010 (Box 31, Folder 198)
  - High Museum of Art - Cecilia Beaux, American Figure Painter, 1855-1942, 2003-2007 (Box 32, Folder 199)
  - High Museum of Art - The Treasure of Ulysses Davis, 2007-2010 (Box 32, Folder 200)
  - Historic New England - Drawing Toward Home: Designs for Domestic Architecture from Historic New England, 2007-2010 (Box 32, Folder 201)
  - The Hong Kong American Center, Ltd. - Advanced Workshop in Western Art and Art History, 2010-2012 (Box 32, Folder 202-203)
  - Hong Kong Baptist University - History of Christianity in China Archive, 1997-2012 (Box 32, Folder 204)
  - Hood Theological Seminary - Library Acquisitions and Services for the New Doctor of Ministry Program, 2002-2010 (Box 32, Folder 205)
  - Huazhong Normal University - History of Christian Universities in China, 1992-2012 (Box 33, Folder 206-207)
  - Huntington Museum of Art - Travelling Exhibition of the American Collection (American Collections Enhancement Initiative), 2000-2005 (Box 33, Folder 208)
  - Institute for Women and Technology - Women in Engineering, 2003-2011 (Box 33, Folder 209)
  - Institute of International Education - Art History in China (Fulbright Program), 2004-2011 (Box 33, Folder 210-212)
  - International Center of Photography - Richard Avedon: Fashion Photographs, 1944-2000, 2008-2010 (Box 34, Folder 213)
  - International House - Scholarship Funds for China Residents, 1999-2011 (Box 34, Folder 214)
  - Inter-American Dialogue - China-Latin America Relations, 2007-2010 (Box 34, Folder 215-216)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange, Inc. - China, Japan, United States Research and Dialogue Project, 2008-2011 (Box 34, Folder 217)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange, Inc. - China, Japan, United States Relations, 2006-2011 (Box 34, Folder 218)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Advanced International Studies - Myanmar/Burma: Outside Interests, Inside Challenges Conference, 2009-2010 (Box 35, Folder 219)
  - King Baudouin Foundation - Modern Life: Edward Hopper and His Time, Kunsthal Rotterdam, Netherlands, 2009-2010 (Box 35, Folder 220)
  - Lafayette College - The Vase Project: Made in China - Landscape in Blue, Williams Center for the Arts Gallery, 2011-2012 (Box 35, Folder 221)
  - LaGuardia Community College Foundation - Efforts to Place Outstanding Graduates in Four-Year Colleges, 2009-2010 (Box 35, Folder 222)
  - LaGuardia Community College Foundation - The MAP: Exploring Transfer (hosted by Vassar College) (Box 35, Folder 222)
  - Lawrence University - Water Resource Management in Wisconsin and China, 2009-2010 (Box 35, Folder 223)
  - James E. Lewis Museum of Art, Morgan State University - William H. Johnson National Exhibition Tour, 2008-2011 (Box 35, Folder 224)
  - Lontar Foundation - Anthology of Indonesian Drama, 2001-2010 (Box 35, Folder 225-226)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art - California Design, 1930-1965: Living in a Modern Way, 2010-2012 (Box 36, Folder 227)
  - Louisville Seminary - Library Automation (Presbyterian Theological Seminary and Southern Baptist Theological Seminary), 1993-1999 (Box 36, Folder 228)
  - American Friends of the Louvre - American Art in French Public Collections, 2006-2014 (Box 36, Folder 229)
  - American Friends of the Louvre - Fellowship to Inventory and Study American Art, 2004-2006 (Box 36, Folder 230-231)
  - American Friends of the Louvre - La Fayette Database of American Art (Phase II), 2009-2010 (Box 36, Folder 232)
  - Madison Square Park Conservancy - Mad. Sq. Art Program 2008, 2007-2009 (Box 36, Folder 233)
  - Madison Square Park Conservancy - Mad. Sq. Art Program 2009, 2008-2009 (Box 36, Folder 234)
  - Madison Square Park Conservancy - Mad. Sq. Art Program 2010, 2009-2011 (Box 37, Folder 235)
  - Madison Square Park Conservancy - Mad. Sq. Art Program 2011, 2010-2011 (Box 37, Folder 236)
  - Mansfield Center for Public Affairs - Trilateral Retreats: Toward New Regional Relations in Northeast Asia, 2003-2011 (Box 37, Folder 237)
  - Mansfield Foundation - Asian Maritime Territorial Disputes and the Law of the Sea Conference, University of Hong Kong, 2011-2012 (Box 37, Folder 238)